http://www.intrafish.no/privacy/

Kontakt
Guided by our principles as a global news service, Intrafish champions transparency, integrity and openness.
That's why we welcome the new data privacy laws, they extend our valued customers greater choice.
We know how important your personal data is to you. In line with this, we have collected all the information you need on privacy here on these pages. Subscribers with user-ids can manage their settings, and the current Privacy and Cookie policies are listed together with previous versions.  If you wish to contact us regarding anything concerning personal data, please use the contact form on the Contact page.
Om personvern
Personvernerklæring
Informasjonskapsler
Mine innstillinger
Kontakt
Kapitteloversikt
Privacy Policy for NHST Global Publications AS
1. About NHST Global Publications, the Services and registrants
2. Why do we process your personal data?
3. Overview of NHST Global Publications’ processing basis
4. The data that are processed
5. Where is the information gathered from
6. Our relationship with third parties
7. Deleting and storing your personal data
8. Your rights
9. Safety and security
Appendix 1. Legitimate interest
Appendix 2. Overview of data processors
Appendix 3. Overview of Adtech suppliers
Privacy Policy for NHST Global Publications AS
1. About NHST Global Publications, the Services and registrants
2. Why do we process your personal data?
3. Overview of NHST Global Publications’ processing basis
4. The data that are processed
5. Where is the information gathered from
6. Our relationship with third parties
7. Deleting and storing your personal data
8. Your rights
9. Safety and security
Appendix 1. Legitimate interest
Appendix 2. Overview of data processors
Appendix 3. Overview of Adtech suppliers
Privacy Policy for NHST Global Publications AS
Revision August 11 2020
This privacy policy applies to all our end users. We want you to have as much control over your personal data as you possibly can, and over how they are treated. You’ll find information on this in this privacy policy. You will also find contact information if you have questions on our processing of personal data. The information is also accessible though the customer service pages.
1. About NHST Global Publications, the Services and registrants
1.1 Who are we?
This privacy policy applies when we, i.e. NHST Global Publications AS, company registration no. 937 593 821, and related publications, IntraFish Media, Upstream, Recharge and TradeWinds («NHST Global Publications ») process your personal data. Consequently, this privacy policy explains why NHST Global Publications gathers information about you, how that information is used, and how NHST Global takes your privacy into account. Your data are safe with us and are only used for what is stated in this policy.
NHST Global Publications AS is wholly owned by NHST Media Group AS («NHST»). NHST and its subsidiaries will hereinafter be called «the Group». You will find information about the Group at
www.nhst.com
. Since the Group uses the same basic information systems and has common technical platforms and IT department, personal data can be processed by the Group for administrative purposes.
1.2 The Services
The privacy policy explains how NHST Global Publications and NHST Global Publications’ partners gather and use personal data when you register with and use NHST Global Publications’ mobile applications («the Apps»), NHST Global Publications’ physical newspapers and magazines («Newspapers»), newsletters («Newsletters»), NHST Global Publications’ conference products, of which NHST Global Publications is the organizer («the conferences»), and websites linked to NHST Global Publications, including the Jobs and Careers sites («the websites»). Hereinafter together these are called «the Services». This privacy policy also explains your privacy-related rights towards NHST Global Publications and NHST Global Publications’ partners. The Services are owned and run by NHST Media Group AS. Its registered address is Christian Krohgs gate 16, 0186 Oslo, mailing address P.O. Box 1182, 0107 Oslo, Norway.
1.3 Whose personal data we process
NHST Global Publications has several groups of end users. If you visit or use NHST Global Publications’ Services, you will belong to one of those groups of end users. The General Data Protection regulations defines you as a «registrant» when you are an end user and identifiable individual with personal data processed.
Which personal data that are processed regarding which users will be further described in chapter 4.
Subscribers
NHST Global Publications processes the most personal data on active subscribers, those who have a subscription where they or their employer pay for the Services, and thy actively use the Services.
Passive subscribers (previous subscribers)
If you have cancelled your subscription for one of NHST Global Publications’ services and 12 months have passed since you cancelled it, you are considered a passive user. In that case, NHST Global Publications will keep some personal data for a certain period of time, as explained in the points below. After that, we will keep some data as provided by law. Other data and purposes we will ask for you consent to store and process further.
Registered users
You can also be a registered user without having a subscription for NHST Global Publications’ Services. This will be the case if you receive a Newsletter or have registered for a trial access to the Services.
Unregistered users
Unregistered users are those who visit any of the Services but neither register nor pay for using them. NHST Global Publications processes very little personal data on this group of users.
Conference users
If you register for a conference organized by NHST Global publications we process data in connection with the registration for and participation at the conference.
Job applicants
When you submit a job application or create a job alert thought the Jobs or Career services, you will be registered in the Service with your email address. We will also store information related to your person if you create a user account in addition.
2. Why do we process your personal data?
NHST Global processes personal data on you for these overall purposes:
In order to be able to deliver and invoice the Services
In order to personalize them for your purposes.
In order to ensure compliance with our terms and conditions.
In order to maintain and further develop the Services.
In order to communicate with your regarding your subscription, editorial content and relevant offerings.
In order to provide, personalize and measure the effect of advertising.
More about purpose no.
1:
NHST Global Publications processes your personal data in order to be able to provide you with the Services and fulfil any customer agreements we have with you. This includes for instance giving you access to the Services, allowing you to administer your user and customer relations, delivering newspapers or magazines to your address, sending invoices and reminders to your email address, and informing you about important matters related to your customer relationship or the Services.
More about purpose no. 2:
NHST Global Publications also uses data about you to be able to personalize the Services to your user profile, for example by customizing some of the content that is shown to you. Profiling means that we create a profile on your user, based on information we have about you and your use of the Services. Through profiling we can personalize the content, adverts and marketing of NHST Global Publications’ Services, to make it more useful and interesting for you.
More about purpose no. 3:
Data about you is also used to prevent misuse of the Services. Misuse may be attempts at logging onto other people’s accounts, trying to swindle people, “spamming”, hate messages, harassment, and other acts that are forbidden according to relevant legislation and our terms and conditions.
More about Purpose no 4:
NHST Global Publications uses data about you and your use of the Services to make sure you get an optimal user experience, and to learn more about how we can and should develop the Services further.
More about purpose no. 5:
NHST Global Publications uses data about you for direct communication and marketing purposes through traditional channels like emails, text messaging, letters and telephone calls, unless you have opted out from such communication or in other ways have withdrawn your consent.
More about Purpose no. 6:
NHST Global Publications is partly financed by advertising revenue and is therefore dependent on providing, personalizeing and measuring the effect of adverts and other marketing in the Services. This is done internally at NHST Global Publications within the Group and in collaboration with third parties, for example like Google Ireland Ltd, as described in more detail in chapter 4-6 and in the paragraphs here.
The data are also used by us and our advertisers, restricted to the Services for profile and segment-based marketing, further developing targeted advertising products, programmatic advertising, automatic marketing, and so-called «retargeting».
By «Programmatic advertising» we mean automated trading of digital advertising via an exchange where we make available our ad impression inventory, and the advertisers can place bids on the impressions based on their criteria. Ads are served real-time. By «Retargeting» we mean repeated and targeted advertising towards an end-user.
3. Overview of NHST Global Publications’ processing basis
Any processing of personal data requires a legal basis. This means that before NHST Global Publications starts processing your personal data, we must ensure that we are entitled to carry out that processing (that NHST Global Publications has a legal basis). That basis may come directly from you for instance in the form of an agreement with us (for instance our subscription terms), or in the form of an active consent (for instance if you have accepted receiving offers via email from us while being a non-subscriber). Here is an explanation of what bases NHST Global Publications uses to process personal data and when we use them.
NHST Global Publications neither can, nor will we, process other personal data about you than what is expressly stated, and neither can nor will we do it in other ways than those described in this policy.
3.1 Agreement
If you are a registered user or an active user with NHST Global Publications, then NHST Global Publications must be able to process personal data on you in order to be able to fulfil the user agreement with you. It is only the processing that is necessary for meeting NHST Global Publications’ obligations under the agreement that is carried out with this processing basis.
What processing is necessary to fulfil the agreement will depend on the user agreement between you and NHST Global Publications. The user agreement will either be “Subscription terms and conditions” or “Terms for registered users”. The agreement will vary somewhat for end users, based on what kind of subscription is agreed. Your user agreement will be available and you should read it before you accept the agreement. The user agreement will also be accessible on your profile page, “My Page” and on subscription information pages on the websites.
One example of processing based on an agreement: If you have a subscription with NHST Global Publications for delivery of a newspaper to your door, NHST Global Publications needs to know the address the paper should be delivered to. Another example is that NHST Global Publications has to process personal data in order to have the correct invoice sent out and make sure it is paid.
3.1.1 Newsletters and notices
A daily newsletter and a weekly hand-picked selection of articles from the Editor-in-Chief is included in your subscription to any NHST Global Publications title. You may cancel these newsletters easily via the newsletters themselves. NHST Global Publications may also publish other types of newsletters and notices from our newsrooms, which you as a registered user can choose to sign up for. You will not receive such other types of regular newsletters unless you actively sign up for them. You control the sign-up or if you want to you can cancel it freely yourself on «My Page» or via the newsletter itself.
3.2 Legitimate interest
Moreover, NHST Global has a legitimate interest in some forms of processing, such as advertising purposes, marketing purposes etc. Such processing based on a legitimate interest applies to users with a registered profile or a subscription, or passive users (former subscribers) as described in chapter 1.3).
If you want to read more about the assessment NHST Global Publications has made, the balance test of your privacy weighed against NHST Global Publications’ legitimate interest, the measures implemented to reduce the risk of processing, and the conclusion on legitimate interest, you will find it in Appendix 1.
For end users with a user profile your settings on your Dashboard will show that the processing of your data that NHST Global Publications has a legitimate interest in carrying out, are “switched on”.
You have a right to «Opt out», which means that you are allowed reserve yourself against the processing, as described in point 8. This means that you can choose to switch off this processing in the settings on your Dashboard if you do not want NHST Global Publications to carry out the processing. Alternatively, you can always contact NHST Global Publications via the
Contact page.
NHST Global Publications does not have any terms and conditions linked to such opting out, but we would like to make it clear that the user experience of the Services may be affected for those who use their right to opt out or withdraw consent.
3.3 Consent
You are free to use the Services without giving us your consent to process your personal data. The Services may lose some functionality and user friendliness without certain consents. Another example is that we have to have consent to be able to send you good offers when you are no longer considered to be an active user.
Consent can also be regulated by you in your settings on the Dashboard, where you will get the opportunity to give consent, see what consents you have given before, and withdraw consents if you change your mind.
3.3.1 Cookies
NHST Global Publications uses information that we gather from our own and third parties’ cookies, tracking pixels and other tracking technology integrated into the Services. This processing applies to all groups of end users of the relevant Services.
When you access and start using the Websites or the Newsletters or when you download and start using the Apps, or use the Services in some other way, you are consenting to NHST Global Publications, the Group and NHST Global Publications’ partners processing data about you, as described in this privacy policy.
If your browser allows information files, so-called cookies, this is considered as your having given us consent to using cookies as stated in this privacy policy. Please also see our
Cookie Policy
. However, we wish to inform you that certain parts of the Services’ functionality depend on such consent and that your access to and experience as a user of the Services could therefore be affected.
3.4 Legislation
NHST Global Publications is required by law to carry out certain processing of personal data, for instance any personal data that NHST Global Publications has to process in order to comply with its accounting and book-keeping obligations.
4. The data that are processed
4.1 Data that is processed about everyone using the Services:
Information that is available on your device and its internet connections, such as for example the name of the maker of your mobile phone/PC, operating system and browser version, e-mail client, and information on the connection with the Services, such as IP-addresses, network ID, cookies and unique identification files.
Statistics on your use of the Services, such as for instance how often various button or links are pressed, purchases that are completed, what pages are visited, when and for how long they are visited, cross-device-tracking for logged-in users, etc.
Statistics on interaction over adverts, newsletters and surveys displayed in the Services.
The location of the unit you use, if such information is shared by the unit.
The information given in the above points is basically not connected with your identity, but is treated as anonymized or pseudonymized data about one of NHST Global Publications’ users. You can limit such storage by surfing in so-called «Private Mode»/«Incognito Mode» when you aren’t logged in. You can also choose to use the «Do Not Track»-function in your browser, or change your privacy settings when you are logged in.
If you register as a customer or user of the Services, any data stored will be linked to our customer relationship or your user, as mentioned in the above points.
4.2 Data that are processed in addition for various end-users
:
In addition to the information mentioned in 4.1, we may process personal data about the various end-users as described here:
4.2.1 Subscribers
If you register as a customer or user of the Services, stored information as described in the items above may be connected to your user account. We process the following data, depending on whether you are a subscriber or registered user:
Name*
Address
Email address*
Telephone/mobile number
Newsletter settings
Employer or other sponsor
Payment information
Information about your customer relationship, such as the type of subscription you have and what newsletters you may receive, payment data and history.
Information on where you learned about NHST Global Publications AS offerings
Your interests, if you have informed us about those
* = required in order to complete your registration.
4.2.2 Registered users
Email address*
Name*
Telephone/mobile number
Newsletter settings
* = required in order to complete your registration.
4.2.3 Registered users with jobs and careers sites
Email address*
Name*
Telephone/mobile number
Profile information
Applications
4.2.4 Conference delegates
Name*
Email address*
Address
Telephone/mobile number
Position
Employer
Payment information
* = required in order to complete your registration.
5. Where is the information gathered from
NHST Global Publications processes personal data on you which you yourself have given to us or through your use of the Services, to which NHST Global Publications gets access from the unit on which you use the Services and which NHST Global Publications collects from third parties as described in this privacy policy.
6. Our relationship with third parties
6.1 Who helps NHST Global Publications in processing your personal data
?
In order to provide you with the Services NHST Global Publications uses several services delivered by third parties. This means that some of these third parties process data on you on our behalf. Third parties who process personal data on behalf of NHST Global Publications are called data processors, in Appendix 2 you will find an up-to-date overview of such data processors.
NHST Global Publications has data processor agreements with third parties that process personal data on our behalf in accordance with current legal requirements.
6.2 To whom does NHST Global Publications pass on personal data?
NHST Global Publications uses a number of services provided by third parties who use information on our users without linking such information to you as an individual. NHST Global Publications’ implementation of such services is done in such a way that this does not mean that personal data about you is processed or transferred by NHST Global Publications. Those NHST Global Publications gives personal data to are not to be able to use your personal data to enrich their own profile sets.
NHST Global uses Google AdX, Google Ad Manager and Google Ads to supply, personalize and measure the effect of adverts in the Services. To ensure that information used in connection with this is anonymous, we follow Google’s
Best practices to avoid sending Personally Identifiable Information (PII)
. You will find an overview of our approved Adtech providers in Appendix 3 of this policy. For further information on Google’s services, technology and use of data, click
here
. You can also choose to opt out of the collection and use of information for ad targeting by other players
here
.
NHST Global Publications does not link information from said third party services to you as a person and has implemented these on account of your privacy. If you have a separate user account with said service providers and are logged in on such user accounts when using the Services, these service suppliers can, in certain cases, link information about your use of the Services to your user account with them. The service provider is responsible for the processing in such cases and their terms and conditions apply. You can change the user settings linked to Google
here
. Google has also explained how you as the end user can remove unwanted ads on
Block off certain ads
.
Active interaction with such Services, for example by clicking on ads and links, can transfer you to sites, applications or services not owned by NHST Global Publications. In such cases other terms and conditions apply, not those of NHST Global Publications.
7. Deleting and storing your personal data
Your personal data will only be stored for as long as we have a legal basis for it in compliance with this privacy policy and current legislation as such. When there is no longer any legal basis for processing, the data will be deleted, encrypted or anonymized.
NHST Global Publications automatically deletes all personal data stored on you after the customer relationship has ceased, and we no longer have legal basis to process your data. We will keep your data further only if you have given your consent for us to do so. Special legal requirements such as accounting obligations and similar demand that certain data are stored longer. Such data will not be used for any other purposes, and during the period leading up to the deletion of such information there will be limited access to such data, and they will be secured by appropriate technical and organizational means.
8. Your rights
You can at any time withdraw the consent you have given under this privacy policy or in some other way to NHST Global Publications. We make it just as easy for you to withdraw your consent as it is for you to give it. Your privacy settings are managed on your
My Settings page
in the Privacy Dashboard.
Such withdrawal can also be done by cancelling any customer relationships you have with us where you ask us to have your user account deleted. To delete anonymized information on your use of the Service, you also have to delete cookies on the unit/your browser. Withdrawal of consent does not affect the legality of the processing built on consent until the consent is withdrawn.
You can also withdraw your consent by contacting NHST Global Publications AS via the
Contact page
or email
NHST Global Publications’ Privacy Officer
.
You can also get in touch with NHST Global Publications in the same way if you want to look into which of your personal data NHST Global Publications has stored, and if you want to have these personal data transferred to you or to have the data deleted or corrected.
Likewise, you can contact NHST Global Publications if you want to limit NHST Global Publications’ processing of your personal data or if you want to protest against NHST Global Publications’ treatment/processing of your personal data. You are also entitled to complain against our treatment to the Data Protection Agency, which is the supervisory authority, if you believe our treatment is in violation of the legislation.
NHST Global Publications makes use of profiling, limited to such purposes as those stated in points 2 – 4 above.
You can choose for yourself to remove our access to your unit’s location data by switching off the location tools on the unit, or by refusing sharing of such data through your unit’s settings.
If NHST Global Publications brings this privacy policy up to date, or changes it, NHST Global Publications will inform you about the changes. Please see the overview of previous versions of this privacy policy.
9. Safety and security
NHST Global has technical and organizational safety measures, including procedures for internal control and information security in accordance with the current privacy rules in Norway.
It is safe to use the Services. NHST Global Publications handles personal data in an encrypted and safe manner for instance by using HTTPS communication for transferring data on you safely and securely.
NHST Global Publications will not sell, replace or disclose your personal data to third parties other than that which is stated in this privacy policy.
Appendix 1. Legitimate interest
NHST Global Publications has conducted an independent evaluation with a balance test and concluded that NHST Global Publications has a legitimate interest to process some personal data.
Legitimate interest
NHST Global Publications has a legitimate interest for digital advertising delivered through the NHST Global Publications Services (Apps, Newspapers, Newsletters, Conferences, and Websites) via an advertising management system that uses cookies for profile data about end users. These are used to i) customize advertising based on interest and location, ii) manage advertisement frequency, iii) measure efficiency, iv) report impressions to advertisers/media agencies. The purpose is that NHST Global Publications may deliver efficient and competitive advertising products in a digital advertising economy and subsequently deliver independent journalism and quality content.
When you subscribe to a payable product, including signing up for a trial subscription, NHST Global Publications has a legitimate interest to market our products and services to you in channels like email and telephone, as well as send you notifications on editorial content that we think you will be interested in reading.
NHST Global Publications will also use data from your user profile and navigation to suggest personalised content and offers when you use the Services based on legitimate interest.
Further, NHST Global Publications has legitimate interest to use personal data to improve our Services by using various analytics and test tools, for instance so-called A/B testing. The purpose for this is to improve the user-experience for all our user groups on our Services.
The personal data
The information processed is normal personalia, data about subscriptions and products, behavioural data from navigation and reading patterns or data given directly by the user. NHST Global Publications and its related titles are not processing sensitive data, ref GDPR art. 9 or 10, and NHST Global Publications are not processing personal id numbers or credit card information.
Risk Mitigation
NHST Global Publications has taken steps to reduce the risk in connection with all data processing. This means that all data that potentially are shared with third-parties are pseudonymized and contain few data points, only cookie-ids and if relevant, the name of the segment that the user belongs to. The systems are well secured, both in technical and organizational terms. Data that are processed by third-party suppliers or partners will not be used to enrich any third-party user-profiles for re-targeting or other advertising purposes. NHST Global Publications also offer the possibility to opt-out of all processing based on legitimate interest.
Conclusion
Based on the information stated here, NHST Global Publications and its related titles has conducted a balance test and concluded that NHST Global Publications and its related titles has a legitimate interest to process personal data for the purposes stated here. Your privacy settings are managed on your
My Settings page
in the Privacy Dashboard, and you are free to opt out of any processing at all times.
Appendix 2. Overview of data processors
Adobe
AirBusiness
Aventri
Capana
Cefalo
Comscore
Google
Appendix 3. Overview of Adtech suppliers
Third party vendors or Adtech suppliers can access personal data regarding our users through programmatic advertising on our services. NHST Global Publications AS qualifies and controls which vendors that can place such ads or form part of the programmatic supply chain, and we will not approve suppliers that we don't trust.
Currently we have approved the following:
Google
Adform
Adnami
Adobe Advertising Cloud
AppNexus
(Xandr) Inc
AudienceProject
Bannerflow
The Trade Desk
Tidligere utgave av erklæringen (08.04.2020)
Om personvern
Personvernerklæring
Informasjonskapsler
Mine innstillinger
Kontakt
Chapters
Information files/“cookies”
About cookies
Consent to using cookies
Our use of cookies
Controlling the use of cookies
Type of data that are processed
Information files/“cookies”
This Cookie Policy explains how NHST Global Publications with its related titles IntraFish, Recharge, TradeWinds and Upstream, and NHST Global Publications’ partners use information files (Cookies) in NHST Global Publications mobile applications (“Apps”) and NHST Global Publications websites (“Websites”), hereafter referred to as “Services”).
The services are owned and operated by NHST Global Publications AS, organization number 937 593 821, business address Christian Krohgs gate 16, 0186 Oslo, Norway, mailing address PO Box 1182, 0107 Oslo, Norway. NHST Global Publications AS is wholly owned by NHST Media Group AS (“NHST”). NHST and its subsidiaries will hereafter be referred to as “the Group”. Information on the Group is found on
www.nhst.com
.
About cookies
Information files or cookies are small data or text files which a website stores on your computer or mobile device when you access a site or page. Cookies are used for various purposes, for instance to help the website recognize your device when you return to the service, serve the correct content to you, store information on your preferences and to serve, customize and measure the effect of advertising. Web beacons or other similar files can also do the same thing. We use the term “cookies” in this policy when referring to all files that collect information in this way. Since the Group uses the same basis systems and have common technical platforms, data, including data from cookies, may be processed by the Group for administrative purposes.
Consent to using cookies
When you visit and use the websites, newsletters and download and use the Apps, or in any other way use the Services, you consent to NHST Global Publications and NHST Global Publications' partners place and read cookies on your device as described in this declaration.
NHST Global Publications will not need consent to use cookies solely for the purpose of transferring communication in a digital communication network, which is necessary to deliver the services and based on your request to do so. Consent may be given via a technical preference in your browser or similar in the cases where this is technically possible and efficient. Preferences in your browser that you accept cookies is regarded as giving consent. It’s sufficient to give consent once for the same purpose. You may at any point withdraw your consent by contacting the NHST Global Publications
Privacy Officer
.
Our use of cookies
NHST Global Publications uses cookies about you for 3 main purposes:
To deliver and customize the service for you
To maintain and develop the Service
To deliver, customize and measure the efficiency of advertising and other content shown you when you use the Service
More information on these purposes can be found in our
Privacy Policy.
To achieve these purposes we use various types of cookies.
Session based cookies:
Session based cookies are cookies that are automatically deleted when you close your browser. We use these to register when you are online on our digital solutions, and how you navigate, for instance while using your profile pages on NHST Global Publications sites.
Fixed cookies:
Fixed cookies are used to collect information on authentication, language and other preferences and settings. Fixed cookies aren’t deleted when you exit the browser, but on a later designated date, or when you delete them yourself. By using these fixed cookies, we optimize the performance of our services and can make sure your log-in details and preferences are remembered the next time you log on. We also use them to track your use of the website and to remind you to update your subscription details from time to time.
Cookies placed by our partners:
To deliver, customize and measure the efficiency of advertising, we have given our advertising partners access to placing and reading cookies. Such third-party cookies can be both session-based or fixed and may be used to collect information about you. If you click on links provided by a third party, terms and conditions for these third-party suppliers apply, including their cookie policies.
For more information about cookies placed by our partners, see our
Privacy Policy
, where you will also find information on how you can opt-out of collection and analysis of data and customized advertising from our partners.
Controlling the use of cookies
You ma at any point disable cookies by choosing this in your browser. These settings are usually found in the “internet options” or “tools” menus in the browser.
We would like to point out that there are tools that can monitor and give you overview about which cookies are placed by the web services you visit. To read more about cookies and how you delete them, see for instance
www.aboutcookies.org
or
www.allaboutcookies.org
. You may also opt out of collection and use of information for customized advertising for other parties, read more about it
here
and
here
.
Please note that some of our functionality and Services will not function if you disable cookies. Your browser will for example not remember your credentials automatically.
Type of data that are processed
A cookie typically contains anonymous data about the use of the Service so that NHST Global Publications and NHST Global Publications' partners can’t identify you as a user. A cookie may nevertheless in some cases contain personal data such as name, log-in credentials necessary for using the Service, device data, your preferences for using the Service, together with information that together with other sets of data may identify you.
Further information about our use of cookies, including which types of cookies that are uses, which data that are processed, the purposes and which parties that are involved in processing them, can be found in our
Privacy Policy
.
Please make sure you are logged in to the service in order to have access to your privacy settings.
Registered users without a password can manage their privacy settings here.
Om personvern
Personvernerklæring
Informasjonskapsler
Mine innstillinger
Kontakt
Please note that only subscribers with a user-id and password have access to this privacy settings page.
Registered users without a password can manage their privacy settings here.
Om personvern
Personvernerklæring
Informasjonskapsler
Mine innstillinger
Kontakt
Accessing your data
As a subscriber or registered user of any of the NHST Global Publications, you have the right to access and review the data we store about you at any time.
We seek to respond access to requests within 30 days, with users receiving a comprehensive audit of the data held by registered mail. You can also request to your data exported in a portable format, such as csv, txt, etc.
Deleting your data
NHST Global Publications applies strict internal controls to ensure your data is stored safely in compliance with the General Data Protection Regulation Act.
We use encryption, process data in a safe manner and automatically delete personal data that falls outside the remit of the regulations.
Under the act, you can request that your personal data is deleted at any time and without undue delay.
If you wish to delete or change the personal data we hold, use the contact form here, or email the Privacy Officer.
NHST Global Publications is required to retain certain data under the Bookkeeping Act, but you will be informed if that is the case.
Navn
E-post
Hva lurer du på?
Send
